https://www.fkabrands.com/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy
California residents, there is specific language using definitions required by California law that you may review on our California Privacy Rights page.
Protecting your privacy is important to FKA Distributing Co., LLC. and its U.S. subsidiaries including HoMedics USA, House of Marley and Truffle Holdings (hereinafter the "FKA Brands"). We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the FKA Brands Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.
FKA Brands complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. FKA Brands communications are subject to jurisdiction under the US Federal Trade Commission and has certified that they adhere to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity access and enforcement. To learn more about the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework, and to view the Companies’ certification, please visit www.privacyshield.gov/welcome.
This Privacy Policy sets forth the privacy principles that FKA Brands follows with respect to personal information transferred from the European Union (EU) to the United States and is in accordance with the agreed upon framework (the “Privacy Shield Framework”) between the US Department of Commerce and the European Commission. FKA Brands complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. FKA Brands is subject to jurisdiction under the US Federal Trade Commission and has certified that they adhere to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield framework of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity access and enforcement.
If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern.
Why we collect personal information
When you shop with FKA Brands, we receive information about you:
Name
Email Address
Phone Number
Postal Address
FKA Brands collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, promotions, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products. Moreover, we may collect your billing and shipping information for processing an online purchase.
How we collect personal information
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we ask for your contact information when you correspond with us or ask to be included in an email mailing list. We collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.
Our Ellia App requires that you allow us access to your camera and photos. The Ellia App captures an image and deletes the image captured within the amount of time it takes the App to recognize the color from your surroundings and match it to the mood light on your Ellia Aroma Diffuser, generally several seconds.
When we disclose personal information
Your personal information may be shared with other FKA Brands business units. They will protect your personal information in accordance with the FKA Brands Customer Privacy Policy.
FKA Brands also works with other companies that help us provide products and services to you, and we may provide your personal information to these companies. For example, we give shipping companies this information so they can deliver your refills or replacement products efficiently. The information they receive is for shipping and delivery purposes only, and we require that the companies safeguard your personal information in accordance with our policies.
Personal data shared with third-parties includes:
Name
Email Address
Phone Number
Postal Address
Payment Information
FKA Brands will always ask for your consent before sharing your Personal Information with a Third Party for purposes other than those described in this section.
At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. FKA Brands is required to disclose Personal Information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
How we protect your personal information
FKA Brands places safeguards to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access and alteration of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet.
Our website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information, including your credit card number, before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions.
FKA Brands is responsible for all transfers of Personal Information to third parties in accordance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles through legally-binding contracts. Any Personal Information transferred to a third party for data processing is processed in accordance with the contract, and is subject, by law, to a comparable level of protection as that provided by FKA Brands.
FKA Brands will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee that FKA Brands determines is in violation of this policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment. FKA Brands will conduct an annual review to ensure adherence to the Privacy Shield framework requirements and complaint handling procedures.
Access to your personal information
You retain all rights to your Personal Information and can access, amend, and correct it anytime.
You always have access to the information we have about you. If you would like to review personal information that FKA Brands may have about you, email us at privacy@fkabrands.com.
How to withdraw your consent
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at privacy@fkabrands.com or mailing us at:
FKA Brands
Privacy Department
3000 N. Pontiac Trail
Commerce Township, MI 48390
Collecting other personal information
When you browse the FKA Brands web sites, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse - not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.
Like many web sites, the FKA Brands web sites use "cookie" technology. When you first connect to our site, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our web sites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.
In some of our email to you, we use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URLs, you pass through our web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. We track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications.
Our company-wide commitment to privacy
To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every FKA Brands employee. FKA Brands does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.
If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.
The FKA Brands Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
Please contact privacy@fkabrands.com to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit privacy-related questions or complaints about privacy.
If you believe your Personal Information has been used in a manner not consistent with the policies outlined, please contact us using the information provided above. If your complaint remains unresolved, you may also contact the International Centre for Dispute Resolution®, the international division of the American Arbitration Association® (ICDR/AAA). This organization provides independent dispute resolution services, at no charge to you. ICDR/AAA can be contacted at go.adr.org/privacyshield.html
If, after attempting to resolve a dispute through ICDR/AAA, you feel that your concerns about the use of your Personal Information have not been resolved, you may seek resolution of the issue through binding arbitration. For more information about the binding arbitration process, please visit www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction.
FKA Brands will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee that FKA Brands determines is in violation of this policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment. FKA Brands will conduct an annual review to ensure adherence to the Privacy Shield framework requirements and complaint handling procedures.
© 2020 FKA Brands - All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy |  UK Modern Slavery Statement | California Privacy RightsDo Not Sell My Personal Information
